<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<data>
  <content>
    <title>Satisfying Videos</title>
    <paragraph>We are here to serve your video spokesperson needs. The exceptional quality of our videos is matched by our spokespeople's talent and our production staff's dedication to ensuring your satisfaction.</paragraph>
  </content>
  <content>
    <title>Spokesperson</title>
    <paragraph>As the online face of your business, a video spokesperson can deliver the exact message you want your visitors to hear. Our web spokesperson actors will impress your customers and increase your bottom line</paragraph>
  </content>
  <content>
    <title>eLearning Spokesperson</title>
    <paragraph>There are a variety of terms used to describe a spokesperson. These include: Talking Video, Avatar, Greeter, Virtual Assistant, Walk-on Actor, Virtual Presenter etc.</paragraph>
  </content>
  <content>
    <title>Make eLearners Comfortable</title>
    <paragraph>A virtual spokesperson is the best way to help your eLearners feel comfortable and engaged with your system. Our combination of price and quality is unmatched, so get started today.</paragraph>
  </content>
  <content>
    <title>Video Solutions</title>
    <paragraph>There are other companies you can choose who charge higher prices and require complex setup solutions for their eLearning Spokespeople. We focus on providing a low cost solution!</paragraph>
  </content>
  <content>
    <title>Amazing Features</title>
    <paragraph>We offer amazing features at the lowest price. Compare our features with the competition, and decide for yourself!</paragraph>
  </content>
  <content>
    <title>Our Spokespeople</title>
    <paragraph>Our spokespeople are experienced professionals with a wide-range of backgrounds and training in spokesmodeling, acting, broadcast journalism, television, on camera promotions, and live performance.</paragraph>
  </content>
  <content>
    <title>eLearning Video</title>
    <paragraph>Add a Spokesperson to your eLearning system to increase viewer attention and comprehension.  Studys show that people pay attention to video more than just text.</paragraph>
  </content>
  <content>
    <title>Professional Spokespeople</title>
    <paragraph>There are many terms for a Video Spokesperson but, matter what term you wish to use:We love to talk with you about your ideas of using a video spokesperson with your eLearning System.</paragraph>
  </content>
  <content>
    <title>Customer Service</title>
    <paragraph>We are committed to all of our customers. Our friendly and knowledgeable video specialists will happily answer any questions you have and help you with your video needs before, during, and after the quick and easy ordering process. </paragraph>
  </content>
  <content>
    <title>Quality Videos</title>
    <paragraph>We pride ourselves on our high quality and successful actors and actresses and all our videos are all shot and built here at our headquarters to maintain quality and precision. It is all filmed HERE.</paragraph>
  </content>
</data>
